[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "How are you bearing up with this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "bearing", "up", "with", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "My faith.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "faith", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "How did you hear the news?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "hear", "the", "news", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "The police officer was trying to locate me for four hours and finally got my telephone number from someone and called me while I was at work, which he didn't know I was at work.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "police", "officer", "was", "trying", "to", "locate", "me", "for", "four", "hours", "and", "finally", "got", "my", "telephone", "number", "from", "someone", "and", "called", "me", "while", "I", "was", "at", "work", ",", "which", "he", "did", "n't", "know", "I", "was", "at", "work", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "RB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "How did you feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Well, I was upset, but I realized, you know, our youth today are young and stupid, and we was all once that age and we'd done things that we are not proud of.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "upset", ",", "but", "I", "realized", ",", "you", "know", ",", "our", "youth", "today", "are", "young", "and", "stupid", ",", "and", "we", "was", "all", "once", "that", "age", "and", "we", "'d", "done", "things", "that", "we", "are", "not", "proud", "of", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "That the behavior of the players off the pitch, perhaps, needs more concern?", "question_tokens": ["That", "the", "behavior", "of", "the", "players", "off", "the", "pitch", ",", "perhaps", ",", "needs", "more", "concern", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "We can say yes and then also I think -- I think it's the individual.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "can", "say", "yes", "and", "then", "also", "I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "the", "individual", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry"]}, "docId": "121210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "How would you like him as his mother to be remembered?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "like", "him", "as", "his", "mother", "to", "be", "remembered", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "Well, I would like Jerry to be remembered as his faith in God and being the best of friends and just an all-out scholar.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "like", "Jerry", "to", "be", "remembered", "as", "his", "faith", "in", "God", "and", "being", "the", "best", "of", "friends", "and", "just", "an", "all-out", "scholar", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "A crisis, would you say?", "question_tokens": ["A", "crisis", ",", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "I don't know if it approaches crisis, perhaps it does but it's at a crossroads because there's an issue about the fundamental nature of the game.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "it", "approaches", "crisis", ",", "perhaps", "it", "does", "but", "it", "'s", "at", "a", "crossroads", "because", "there", "'s", "an", "issue", "about", "the", "fundamental", "nature", "of", "the", "game", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "What can you really do about it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "you", "really", "do", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "I'm not sure what can be done about it exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "sure", "what", "can", "be", "done", "about", "it", "exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "I'm not commenting on the exact whys and where fors that will play out in the court of law about what happened between him and Trayvon Martin, but what does common sense tell you about the likelihood of that confrontation ever taking place in the first place if George Zimmerman was not carrying a gun?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "commenting", "on", "the", "exact", "whys", "and", "where", "fors", "that", "will", "play", "out", "in", "the", "court", "of", "law", "about", "what", "happened", "between", "him", "and", "Trayvon", "Martin", ",", "but", "what", "does", "common", "sense", "tell", "you", "about", "the", "likelihood", "of", "that", "confrontation", "ever", "taking", "place", "in", "the", "first", "place", "if", "George", "Zimmerman", "was", "not", "carrying", "a", "gun", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "WRB", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "I couldn't agree more.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "could", "n't", "agree", "more", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Trayvon Martin", "George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "Is it time for him to show some proper moral leadership here, do you think, and actually do something or try and do something?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "time", "for", "him", "to", "show", "some", "proper", "moral", "leadership", "here", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "and", "actually", "do", "something", "or", "try", "and", "do", "something", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "Again, I'm not positioning myself as an expert, but as a private citizen, I would like to see him do that, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Again", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "positioning", "myself", "as", "an", "expert", ",", "but", "as", "a", "private", "citizen", ",", "I", "would", "like", "to", "see", "him", "do", "that", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "Tell me about your journey and why you have ended up now in President Obama's camp?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "about", "your", "journey", "and", "why", "you", "have", "ended", "up", "now", "in", "President", "Obama", "'s", "camp", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "Well, the reason that, as I said at the convention, I didn't leave the Republican party.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "reason", "that", ",", "as", "I", "said", "at", "the", "convention", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "leave", "the", "Republican", "party", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "What do you parents make of your defection?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "parents", "make", "of", "your", "defection", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "They're happy about it.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "happy", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "agree", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "She would be extremely formidable.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "would", "be", "extremely", "formidable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "And what needs to be done to get a deal, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "needs", "to", "be", "done", "to", "get", "a", "deal", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "Well, you couldn't have said it better.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "could", "n't", "have", "said", "it", "better", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "Do you actually that you're all going to rise up one day against a tyrannical presidency in your own country?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "actually", "that", "you", "'re", "all", "going", "to", "rise", "up", "one", "day", "against", "a", "tyrannical", "presidency", "in", "your", "own", "country", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "I would be the first one out there leading the people of this country against a tyrannical government.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "be", "the", "first", "one", "out", "there", "leading", "the", "people", "of", "this", "country", "against", "a", "tyrannical", "government", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "James Fallows, what is your view of that?", "question_tokens": ["James", "Fallows", ",", "what", "is", "your", "view", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "Well, I guess I approach this on two levels.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "guess", "I", "approach", "this", "on", "two", "levels", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["James Fallows"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "I agree.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "agree", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "And what does it tell you about the ongoing conflict in Afghanistan?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "does", "it", "tell", "you", "about", "the", "ongoing", "conflict", "in", "Afghanistan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "Well, first of all, we don't know how the SEAL was killed.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "know", "how", "the", "SEAL", "was", "killed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iraq", "Iraq", "U.S."]}, "docId": "121210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "RBR", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Historically when we look back on this period, notwithstanding the death of bin Laden, do you think that the conflict in Afghanistan will be seen as anything but a rather miserable failure in the end?", "question_tokens": ["Historically", "when", "we", "look", "back", "on", "this", "period", ",", "notwithstanding", "the", "death", "of", "bin", "Laden", ",", "do", "you", "think", "that", "the", "conflict", "in", "Afghanistan", "will", "be", "seen", "as", "anything", "but", "a", "rather", "miserable", "failure", "in", "the", "end", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "I think it will be -- actually, it will be interestingly and maybe more positively paired with the war in Iraq, the war in Iraq being an entirely discretionary war that the U.S. undertook on the basis of incorrect information.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "will", "be", "--", "actually", ",", "it", "will", "be", "interestingly", "and", "maybe", "more", "positively", "paired", "with", "the", "war", "in", "Iraq", ",", "the", "war", "in", "Iraq", "being", "an", "entirely", "discretionary", "war", "that", "the", "U.S.", "undertook", "on", "the", "basis", "of", "incorrect", "information", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "Do you think the politicians understand the kind of seriousness of the game that they're playing at the moment?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "the", "politicians", "understand", "the", "kind", "of", "seriousness", "of", "the", "game", "that", "they", "'re", "playing", "at", "the", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "I think that they do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "they", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "And how will it play out?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "will", "it", "play", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "Let's go prop on you.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "go", "prop", "on", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "Who's going to be top dog in the end, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "top", "dog", "in", "the", "end", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "That's tough.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "tough", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]